koyalwholesale.com 2015-06-10

# Privacy Policy : Wholesale Wedding Supplies, Discount Wedding Favors, Party Favors, and Bulk Event Supplies

(Updated 3/6/2013) 

Thank you for accessing Koyalwholesale.com (“Site”).  We understand you may have concerns about privacy about shopping online.  This Privacy Policy describes how we use and do not use information provided to us and the steps we take to protect it.

## Personal Information We Collect Online

Our goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with an efficient, easy, and customized experience.

When you make a purchase on our Site, we ask for your name, address, phone number, email address and other personal information necessary to fulfill and track your order. For purposes of billing, you will need to provide your credit card type, number, and expiration date as well as the billing address associated with the credit card. If your order is to be shipped, we also need the name, address and phone number of the intended recipient(s).

You also may create an account through our Site at any time by providing your email address and designating a unique access password. Creating an account allows you to save certain billing information so that you can track the status of your orders and set your ordering preferences. However, for your privacy and security, we do not store credit card numbers in your account. You may change saved account information, such as your shipping address or phone number, at anytime. Simply go online, log in with your email address and password, and then click “Account Settings."

By visiting this Site directly or through another site, you accept the practices described in this policy.

We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices on any website not operated by Koyal Wholesale to which the Site links or that links to the Site.

## Cookies and Other Computer Information

When you visit our Site, small text files known as "cookies" will be stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies allow us to enhance and customize your online shopping experience and improve the design of our site. These cookies store random ID numbers and site navigation information such as your first and last visits, number of visits, shopping cart contents, and the pages you viewed on our website. Cookies also may collect certain technical information from your computer. This technical information may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer's operating system, browser type and the address of a referring website, if any. The information stored in a cookie cannot be used to identify you personally unless combined with information that you have provided in connection with a purchase, setting up an account, or registering for promotional emails, contests, or surveys. Although IP addresses alone can reveal the location of your computer, we will use such information only to investigate and identify unauthorized activities.

This Site uses session cookies to observe your navigation throughout the website for the purposes described above. You may set your Web browser to notify you when you receive a cookie and you may also erase cookies from your browser after shopping. If you delete our cookies, you limit our ability to personalize your next shopping visit; however, deleting a cookie will not prevent you from shopping and purchasing at our site in the future. You may also choose to set your Web browser to not accept cookies.

## Information Shared with Third Parties

We do not rent, sell or exchange your name or other personally-identifiable information to third-party companies.  This information may be provided to reputable third party organizations that help us to process and fulfill your order. This information will be used solely for transactional purposes, which includes, but is not limited to using third party companies to verify and process credit card transactions, to perform order fulfillment, to deliver packages, to schedule and perform product installations and to administer service programs. We may share your information with others who help us analyze our sales data, maintain our records, and provide other services for our Site such as collect site navigation information. We may share this information with companies that act on our behalf and at our direction to ship merchandise to you and also notify you of additional Koyal Wholesale products and services. These third parties are not authorized to use your information for any reason other than to perform their contractually assigned functions. We never authorize unsolicited advertising or communication from third party organizations.

We may be required to disclose your personal information to third parties if necessary to comply with applicable laws, subpoenas or court orders.

## Uses of Information Collected Online

Information collected on this Site may be used in the following ways:

  * Schedule deliveries of merchandise that you purchase online
  * Create an online account for you at KoyalWholesale.com
  * Bill your credit card for your purchases
  * Confirm and track your orders
  * Respond to your customer service inquiries
  * Provide promotional communication if you choose to receive them
  * Offer the products you want
  * Customize your shopping experience
  * Improve our website design and helpful features

## Accessing and Updating My Information

You can access and correct information you have shared with us online if you have established an account with KoyalWholesale.com. Simply go to your account, log in with your email address and password, click "Account Settings" and edit or delete whatever information you wish. Do not share your password with anyone.

## Promotional Communications

The personal information you supply us will be added to our customer database. We may send you promotional emails about Koyal Wholesale products, services or contests that we hope will be of interest. At any time, you can choose to discontinue receiving such promotional email. You can instruct us whether you want to receive such emails by removing the mark from the box indicating your preference when prompted.

## Product Reviews

You may choose to submit product reviews at which time you will need to register.  We will ask for your name, email address and geographic location at time of registration.  Once you submit your review, only your first name, last name initial and geographic location (city and state only or city and country if international) will be visible to other users.  Please do not submit any personally identifiable information as a part of the review as it will be visible to other users.  We are not responsible for any personally identifiable information that you choose to submit as part of your review.

## Blog 

If you use a bulletin board, blog, or chat room on this Site or contribute tips for use on this Site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages.  We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums or features.

## Email A Friend

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address.  We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site.  This Site does not store this information and uses it for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.

## Privacy Protection

We protect our databases with strong security measures and we restrict access to your information by unauthorized persons. Our information systems are maintained behind a software firewall to isolate them from access by other networks connected to the Internet. We also advise all our employees about their responsibility to protect customer data and we provide them with appropriate guidelines for adhering to our company's business ethics standards and confidentiality policies.

All information transmitted through this Site is stored on our secure server. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology, which is the electronic commerce standard for securing information as it travels over the Internet. SSL technology is designed to encrypt your information, preventing an unauthorized party from viewing and downloading your information.

## Contact Information

If you have any questions or comments write to us at:

**Koyal Wholesale  
Attention: Customer Service Manager  
2325 Raymer Ave  
Fullerton, CA 92833  
U.S.A.**

Please remember to include your postal address, e-mail address and phone number with your correspondence.

###### Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we change or update this Privacy Policy, we will post the changes and updates on the Site so that you are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it.

Koyal Wholesale is committed to quality customer service and we are constantly reviewing your feedback to improve our services.  Please tell us what you think by emailing us or calling us at 714.459.0600 (Monday-Friday PST) during regular business hours.
